#### Contact

beckyflemingrn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/becky-fleming-registered-nurse (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Physician EMR Training Nursing EMR Training Process Optimization

# Languages

English

#### Certifications

Chemotherapy Certification
Advanced Cardiac Life Support
(ACLS)

Registered Nurse

Stroke Scale Training and Certification

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

# Becky Fleming, RN

Versatile, customer-focused professional nurse with unique experience and skill set.

Milford, Delaware

## Summary

Versatile professional nurse with 10+ years of experience including: Mes-Surg/Oncology Cardiac, Telemetry, Emergency, and Informatics. Recognized for teamwork, team building, and creative problem solving across specialties. Adept Communicator | Creative/Critical Thinker | Highly Skilled Trainer/Educator | Customer-oriented

- At ease sharing essential information with Patients and Families, Nurse Colleagues, Executive Team
   Members, Ancillary Staff, and Medical Providers.
- Utilizes unique experiences and skill sets to approach and solve multi-faceted problems.
- Provides experience-targeted healthcare skills training and education to patient and healthcare provider populations.
- Consistently exceeds expectations for compassionate, skilled nursing care while collaborating with team members across specialties to achieve excellent clinical outcomes.

While providing nursing care fulfills the need to contribute to the community in meaningful ways, Becky is also a passionate, and skilled portrait and nature photographer. Her portraiture focuses on revealing genuine personality, and authentic human nature and interactions. It appeals to clients who are seeking emotional pull in their photographs. Becky's nature photography tends toward close-up work, featuring "small objects and vignettes that might otherwise go unnoticed."

## Experience

MaineGeneral Health Travel Registered Nurse April 2020 - Present (4 months) Augusta, Maine, United States

Provide excellent nursing care for medical-surgical and oncology patient population at a medium sized, rural hospital.

Beebe Healthcare
Registered Nurse
2019 - Present (1 year)
Medical-Surgical/Oncology

After stepping away from bedside hospital nursing I knew I wanted make a gentle re-entry. 3MS at Beebe Healthcare gave me exactly that.

Beck Fleming Photography 7 years 7 months

Portrait Photographer
January 2017 - Present (3 years 7 months)
Milford, Delaware

Documentary-style photographer with an eye for detail. Best known for developing deep connections with clients which results in a unique ability revealing true personalities in portraits.

- Communicates with clients remotely and in-person to develop client profile and custom
- photography and image collections.
- Managed marketing, advertising, accounting aspects of a growing small business.

Fine Art Photographer
January 2013 - Present (7 years 7 months)
Milford, DE • Beacon, NY

Personal projects include fine art nature and close-up photography. I prefer hand-held over the use of a tripod, and natural over artificial light whenever possible. I tend toward close-ups of tiny wildflowers or other objects that might otherwise go unnoticed. When documenting a nature scene, I am drawn to the juxtaposition of the process of decay among the beauty of nature's many moods and colors.

Ecolife Development, Inc.
Project Coordinator
September 2013 - June 2016 (2 years 10 months)
Las Vegas, Nevada Area

Proficient in office management, resource coordination, and collaboration with external resources.

- Implemented project management and accounting applications to improve expense and revenue capture processes.
- Improved efficiency and coordination of outside contractors to assist in delivery on-time commercial construction services.

Conant and Associates, Inc.

Project Manager/Trainer, Clinical Informatics Specialist August 2011 - September 2013 (2 years 2 months)

Western Division

Collaborated with a team of Health and Information Technology (HIT)
Professionals to provide expert Speech Recognition Technology (SRT)
training. Managed internal and client-side teams, timelines, and risks to
successfully implement 30+ projects for this nationally recognized Healthcare
IT corporation.

- Provided expert workflow analysis and customized clinician training for hospital organizations
   nationwide.
- Surveyed 100+ client-side Informatics managers to determine actual usage rates and contributing factors for fall off. Data used to recapture users, improve SRT accuracy, and target sites for

additional training and revenues.

 Coordinated with internal and external resources to manage up to 40 projects monthly using strong communication skills, creative problem solving, and skillful team

building strategies.

### Nanticoke Memorial Hospital

Subject Matter Expert, Registered Nurse - Emergency Department (ED) November 2008 - July 2011 (2 years 9 months)

Seaford, DE

Provided high quality nursing care within this 21 bed Trauma Level 3
Emergency Department. Handled medical emergencies including stroke, cardiac arrest, motor vehicle crashes, gunshot wounds, and accidental amputations.

• Collaborated with medical team to educate, prepare patients, and assist providers with emergent

and non-emergent procedures including cardiac resuscitation, trauma care, wound care and

sutures, chest tube insertions.

 Proficient IV insertions. Recognized by emergency nursing team as a "go-to" resource for difficult

insertion situations.

 Selected to provide Emergency Department subject matter expertise as part of a nursing

informatics team during a one+ year Electronic Medical Record enhancement project.

#### Cerner EHR Enhancement Project:

• Designed process and customized Cerner's Firstnet trackingshell to capture patients' discharge out

of foreign registration system. Departments positively impacted: ED, Registration, Billing.

 Designed process and solution to simultaneously document ECG date/time, complete order, and

drop ED ECG billing charge when ECG form signed by performer.

Departments positively impacted:

ED, Quality, Cardiology, Billing.

• Developed, customized, and presented materials to train physician and nursing staff in preparation

for launch of enhancements including: Bedside Monitor Device Interface (BMDI), Computerized

physician order entry (CPOE), Electronic Medication Administration Record (eMAR), IView, Message

Center, PowerNote ED, and PowerPlans.

Delaware Hospice, Inc.
Primary Registered Nurse
February 2008 - June 2008 (5 months)

Dover, Delaware Area

Provided excellent nursing care, education, and psychosocial support to patients and families during end-of-life.

 Hospice nursing continues to be the most rewarding bedside nursing job, however I was unable to maintain the emotional distance required by the job and my tenure as a nurse with Delaware Hospice was quite short-lived.

Cross Country TravCorps
Travel Registered Nurse

November 2006 - February 2008 (1 year 4 months) Boca Raton, FL

Provided proficient telemetry nursing care to patients with diverse needs, education levels, and socio-economic backgrounds. Commended for consistent, excellent teamwork and collaborative efforts unusual to travel nurses.

 Provided excellent care and timely documentation for three to five acute care/ telemetry patients

with 1st, 2nd, and 3rd degree burns, including: wound care, dressing changes, and intensive

psychosocial support. Prepared and educated patients to continue wound care and dressing

changes at home.

 Used critical thinking and assessment skills to plan, implement, and assess cardiac nursing care plans, and provide proficient patient care for the cardiac observation population at this busy resort-area hospital.

• Offered permanent positions at the termination of both travel contracts.

Christiana Care Health System
Staff Registered Nurse
December 2004 - October 2006 (1 year 11 months)
Newark, DE

Delivered excellent patient care and education to cardiac step-down patient population. Using current nursing standards, provided assessment to patients awaiting or recovering surgery and procedures including: cardiac catheterization, myocardial infarction (MI), coronary artery bypass graft (CABG), cardioversion.

 Performed Charge Nurse duties for this 34 bed Cardiac Step Down (Telemetry) Unit.

Responsibilities included: tracking patient acuity, discharge planning, coordinating with bed

coordination hospital-wide, monitoring telemetry, staff assignments.

 Proficient preceptor to new and onboarding nurses. Tasks included: orienting nurses to unit and procedures, educating, assisting, and encouraging new nurses.

Bayhealth Staff Registered Nurse July 2004 - December 2004 (6 months) Dover, DE

Delivered excellent patient care and education to cardiac step-down patient population. Using current nursing standards, provided assessment to patients awaiting or recovering surgery and procedures including: cardiac catheterization, myocardial infarction (MI), cardioversion.

• Though this hospital was closer to home, I found I enjoyed the challenge and collaboration at

Christiana Care better suited my personal and professional needs. Because of this mismatch, I

returned to Christiana Care after only a few short months.

Christiana Care Health System Staff Registered Nurse June 2003 - June 2004 (1 year 1 month) Newark, DE

As a new nurse graduate, delivered excellent patient care and education to cardiac step-down patient population. Using current nursing standards, provided assessment to patients awaiting or recovering surgery and procedures including: cardiac catheterization, myocardial infarction (MI), coronary artery bypass graft (CABG), cardioversion.

 Consistently recognized as eager to learn and willing to assist wherever needed in this busy cardiac care unit.

## Education

Delaware Technical and Community College-Terry Associate Degree Nursing, Nursing (2000 - 2003)